Hey Damonte, congratulations. Just just
want to ask you how much interaction you
had with the Bucks during the direct
process and whether you might might have
seen the club a little bit.
>> Uh I think it was the most interaction I
had was when I came down my 30 visit u
to the Bucks and it was it went really
well.
>> You put up some some crazy physical
numbers at the coma. Are you more proud
of the 48540 or the 34 inch vertical?
Um,
I'm not really, you know, proud of
nothing. I feel like it's a long ways to
go. But I think, um, I think I was I
knew I could run fast, but I was I was
more probably I probably was more
impressed about that vert, you know, cuz
haven't jumped in so long.
>> Can you just talk about the mentality
you bring when you step on the football
field on on now on Sundays?
>> My mentality that I bring on the field
is violent. You know what I'm saying? I
I I you know with a lot of different
teams you know they got different
schemes or whatever whatnot but me when
I step on the field my my my mentality
is to go through somebody pushing
another grown man against their will
when you look at NFL Dlineman is there
somebody uh in terms of skill set size
just just demeanor on the field is there
somebody you like to watch as as someone
that's close to what what your strengths
are
>> yeah so I like to watch big decks
because I know him personally you know
what I'm saying I I feel like I'm close
reach to that guy. So whenever I have
questions or something, I can always
reach out to him or, you know, so that's
what who I look at and feel like I can
get tips from anytime I need or learning
experience. You know what I'm saying?
Cuz he's been doing it so long. So yeah,
that's that's somebody I look up look up
to.
>> When you look at your your 40th time
vert that athleticism that you displayed
there, how does that how do you use that
on the field to your advantage?
Uh, I mean, of course, like when if I'm
in the B line of the quarterback
throwing the ball, I feel like that
that's a that's a great opportunity to
for me to showcase that uh vertical by
trying to knock it by swatting it down.
Um, in my 40 just uh when when guys see
me, I think running backs like take it
for count like, oh, he's he's big, he
not he not fast. So, I think that's a
attribute that I love showcasing. Um,
you know, to let uh smaller guys know
that I'm not slow. But Damonte, you're
joining a defensive line room with some
serious attitude with Vea and Aan
Robinson who they signed in free agency.
How excited are you to now be in the
mix?
>> Uh, I'm I'm I'm very excited. Um, ready
to um, you know, be a part of that room,
learn from that room, and, you know, cuz
that's a lot of veteran guys just just
want to come be a part and figure out
how to help that help those guys uh,
help help them win.
You have a high school basketball
background, correct?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Can you talk a little bit about how you
feel like that helps you when you're on
the the football field?
>> Uh just, you know, quickness. I think my
first step that helps first step uh just
things of that nature, but um most
importantly footwork
uh with basketball.
>> Can you talk Go ahead.
>> Can you talk about the call uh that when
you receive the call, you're getting
dropped by the Bucks. Where are you?
What was that emotion like? What did
that mean to you? Um, well, I remember
what coach BS told me when I came down
from my 30 visit. It just played in my
head so many times uh that we we was we
would talk again and um that just that
just was one of the things kept playing
in my head when I seen my phone buzzing.
I was like, "Oh my god, no way."
>> Uh, the Bucks defense typically requires
defensive linemen to be very versatile
playing shade three, four eye, five. Is
there a specific position that you get
really excited to get into in terms of a
specific gap and be able to attack from?
>> Me personally, I love it all because
it's just it's all the same thing if you
think about it. You just it's just where
you aligning at. I feel like if if
you're a two eye, you can play the
three. If you're a three eye, you can
play the four. Like it's it's all the
same thing. It's just um it's just
bumping you out out farther away. That's
all I see it as. So, I think I'm very uh
talented and versatile. So, I think I
can play all of them and I'm I'm
excited, you know, when when I So, me
personally, when I get in the nose
position, that's where I feel like I'm
dominant because my quick first step on
the centers and guards and stuff like
that. So, yeah.
>> What would you say your biggest strength
is and and what you're bringing what you
can bring to this team down here in
Tampa Bay?
>> Um, my biggest strength is uh like I
said, being violent uh and just, you
know, stopping the run. And what do you
think you can bring to the the defense?
>> Uh, I think I can bring uh tenacity um
that energy uh that that that that that
swagger um to that defense.
>> When you're defending the run, you got a
double team coming up against you. What
is your I guess go-to way to try and
anchor down and prevent them from
getting vertical displacement on you?
>> What say it again?
>> What's your go-to in terms of trying to
stop double teams from moving you off
your gap? Uh, I like to throw my hip
into the to the go hard or or the the
tackle essentially. Uh, so I just like
to I don't really drop the knee. I
always try to like brace my brace my uh
inside leg and throw my hip into the the
pressure.
>> Appreciate you. Do
>> you had a If you could say anything to
the Bucks fans who are watching right
now, what kind of player, what kind of
person, what are they getting out of
you?
>> Uh, for all the Bucks fan, you you're
getting a guy that's committed. uh a guy
that knows what he wants and know knows
what to bring every single day. A guy
that knows how to work and and a guy
that uh gonna give y'all his all.
>> All right.
Congratulations.
>> Thank y'all. Appreciate y'all. See you
down here in a week. See you.